Would you like to have extra material as exercises for vocabulary and grammar?
Join our membership.
Hello!
Hello Juan!
What are you doing?
Look, this is the plan for my new apartment.
I'm looking where I'm going to accommodate my new furniture.
Do you like it?
Yes, it's a very big apartment, but I don't understand it, do you explain it to
me?
Yes, of course, it's big for me, but you will like it a lot.
Look, this is the entrance and here is a small bathroom.
Bathroom.
Here is a living room with its TV and in the background is a small balcony.
Next to it is the first room.
How many rooms does your apartment have?
My apartment has two rooms. This room is the room for visits.
And this one is my room.
Your room is much bigger than the one you visit.
Yes, my room has its bathroom and also has its closet.
It's very pretty.
And what else is there?
Look, in front of the first room is the kitchen.
It's also very big. I already have a refrigerator, a stove and a small table for
the center.
Look, here is the dining room next to the kitchen.
And this?
This is what I like the most about my new apartment.
It's my garden.
Wow, it's a very big garden.
Yes.
Your entire apartment is very big.
It has an entrance, a bathroom, a living room, a balcony and it has two rooms.
The small room is for visits and the larger room is for a bathroom and a closet.
In front of the room for visits is the kitchen and on the side is the dining
room.
And also my favorite part is the garden.
Yes, the garden is very big.
And I would like you to help me to see what plants I can plant in my new garden.
Of course, I would also like to help you with the change.
Yes, it would be perfect.
Great.
Oh, I love it.
If you liked our video, remember to like it and subscribe to our channel.
And if you want extra material, you can also join our membership.
See you in another video.
Bye.